A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Numerical files, 1979-1999., Extent: 33.3 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 1-74)
  - 42. Roanoke City
    - [42.015] Hotel Roanoke, 1991-1997. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [42.015] Hotel Roanoke, H.B. 135, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [42.015] Hotel Roanoke, H.B. 1795, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - [42.015] Hotel Roanoke, Charter of 1952, 1991. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - [42.015-A] Hotel Roanoke, Opinion of Attorney General, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [42.015-B] Hotel Roanoke, Dedication speech, 1995. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [42.015-C] Hotel Roanoke, Conference Center, 1997. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [42.016] Roanoke Museum of Fine Arts budget request, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - [42.016-A] Roanoke Museum of Fine Arts resolution material, 1991. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - [42.016-B] Roanoke Museum of Fine Arts State appropriation requests, 1992-1994. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - [42.017] H.B. 82 Public works contract, 1990. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - [42.018] Roanoke city public task force, 1990. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - [42.019] Gardner-Denver Mining and Construction, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - [42.020] The New Century Council, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [42.021] Roanoke city taking over Roanoke Gas, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - [42.022] Roanoke Chamber of Commerce, 1994. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - [42.022-A] Roanoke Chamber of Commerce, Incubator, 1994. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - [42.022-B] Roanoke Regional Chamber of Commerce legislative issues, 1995-1997. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - [42.027] Family Assessment Planning Team, ca. 1993. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - [42.029] Roanoke City Council, 1997-1998. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - [42.038] Star Celebration Committee, 1999. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - 43. Roanoke County
    - [43.001] H.B. 66 Amendment to Roanoke County Charter, 1985-1989. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - [43.002] General correspondence, May 1984-March 1986. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - [43.002] General correspondence, April 1986-November 1991. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - [43.003] Roanoke County School, 1986-1991. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - [43.003-A] Roanoke County School funding, 1987-1988. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - [43.003-B] City of Salem legislative issues, 1990. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - [43.003-C] Roanoke Rebos Inc., 1990-1991. (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - [43.004] Roanoke County legislative issues, 1989-1990. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - [43.004-B] Roanoke County resolutions, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - [43.004-C] Town of Vinton charter, 1982. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - [43.004-D] Roanoke County Legislative Program, 1994. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - [43.004-F] City of Salem Legislative Program, 1997. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - [43.004-H] Roanoke County Legislative Program, 1999. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - [43.005] City of Salem Legislative File, 1996. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - [43.006] Regionalization, 1993. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - 44. Veto session
    - [44.003] Veto session, 1989. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - [44.004] Veto session, 1990. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - [44.006] Veto session, 1992. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - [44.007] Veto session, 1993. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - [44.008-B] Reconvened session, 1994. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - [44.009] Veto, 1997. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - 45. Judges
    - [45.002] General correspondence, 1988-1993. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - [45.003] Juvenile and Domestic Relations District Court Judge appointment, 1988-1989. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - [45.004] Judicial appointments, 1989. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - [45.005] Roanoke City Judges Meetings, 1989. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - [45.005-A] Roanoke City Judges Meetings, 1991. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - [45.008] H.B. 1441 Salaries of judges, 1993-1994. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 46. Legislative Services
    - [46.001] Proposed legislation, 1987-1988. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - [46.002] Bill preparations drafts, 1987. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - [46.003] Proposed legislation, 1989. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - [46.004] Bills drafted but not entered, 1989. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - [46.004-A] Bills drafted but not entered, 1990. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - [46.007] Legislative services assignment, 1989. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - [46.008-A] Proposed bills for legislation, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - [46.008-B] Statue of limitations extension for adult victims of child sexual abuse, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - [46.008-C] Liquor by the drink, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - [46.008-D] Habitual offenders, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - [46.008-E] Performance payment bonds, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [46.008-F] Primary and filing schedule for 1991 election, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - [46.008-G] Showtimers of Roanoke Valley, Inc., 1991. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - [46.008-H] Consumer Credit Counseling, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - [46.008-J] Petitions for Adoption and Authority of Judicial Council, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - [46.008-K] Civil actions against Va. Dept. of Transportation, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - [46.008-L] Mechanics Lien Laws, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - [46.008-M] Birth-Related Neurological Injury Study, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - [46.008-O] Vicious dogs and Banquet licenses, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - [46.008-P] Property Owners' Association Act, 1991. (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - [46.008-R] Virginia Home Builders Association, 1991. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [46.008-S] Prescribing authority for nursing practitioners, 1991. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [46.009-A] Issue briefs, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [46.009-B] H.B. 5 Judges' oaths, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - [46.009-C] H.B. 6 Prepayment of fines, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - [46.009-D] H.B. 7 Magistrates, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - [46.009-E] H.B. 8 Prisoners as witnesses, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - [46.009-F] H.B. 9 Judges' and clerks' fees in district courts, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - [46.009-H] H.B. 80 Property tax exemption, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - [46.009-J] H.B. 136 Mental health examinations, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - [46.009-L] H.B. 138 Commitment of convicted person, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - [46.009-M] H.B. 161 Certificates of analysis, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - [46.009-N] H.B. 163 Juvenile courts, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - [46.009-O] H.B. 164 Drunken driving, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - [46.009-P] H.B. 165 Investigation of elected officials, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - [46.009-Q] H.B. 181 Insurable interests of charitable organizations, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - [46.009-R] H.B. 202 State Corporation Commission authority, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - [46.009-S] H.B. 269 Presumption of negligence, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - [46.009-U] H.B. 438 Presentence reports, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - [46.009-V] H.B. 527 Virginia Asbestos Act, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - [46.009-W] H.B. 718 Divorce equitable distribution, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - [46.009-Y] H.B. 720 Membership of Marine Resources Commission, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - [46.009-Z] H.B. 721 Board of Bar Examiners, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - [46.009-2] H.B. 980 Notice required before sale by trustee, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - [46.009-7] Center in the Square budget request, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - [46.009-8] Literacy Volunteers of America, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - [46.009-9] H.B. 1 Animal cruelty, 1992. (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - [46.009-10] Salvage Motor Vehicles Act, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - [46.009-11] City of Salem resolution to become members of Supplemental Retirement System of Va., 1992. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - [46.009-11(2)] Other resolutions- City of Salem, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - [46.009-12] Roanoke County legislative program, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - [46.009-13] Emergency Responders Legislative Coalition, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - [46.009-14] Mobile Health Care Unit, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - [46.009-15] Judgments with regard to interest, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - [46.009-18] Administrative license revocation, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - [46.010-1] H.B. 961, 962 Medical malpractice cap, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - [46.010-4A] Claim bills constitutionality, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - [46.010-6] Inaugural funds, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - [46.010-8] H.B. 1637 Burley tobacco, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [46.010-13] H.B. 2408 Asbestos contractors and workers, 1992. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - [46.010-16] Fulton Motors Change of Statue, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - [46.010-17] S.B. 582 Charter bill Roanoke zoning, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - [46.010-18] H.B. 1768 Pay for penalties, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - [46.011-7] Real estate transfers, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - [46.011-8] Automobile liability insurance increase for DUI convictions, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - [46.011-13] Ineligibility for parole for conviction of third violent felony, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - [46.011-14] Virginia Trial Lawyers Association, 1993. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - [46.011-18] H.B. 246 Compensation of court appointed counsel in capital cases, 1994. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - [46.012-1] Sales tax on charitable donation, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - [46.012-2A] Apprentice programs, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - [46.012-3A] Carry over bills Courts of Justice, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - [46.012-3B] Carry over bills and general laws, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - [46.012-10] Motion in liming, 1994. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - [46.012-12C] City of Roanoke legislative issues, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - [46.012-13] Judgments, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - [46.012-14A] Code amendment 56-265.4:2A, Extension of services by cities and towns into annexed areas, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - [46.012-15A] Charter schools, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - 47. Governor of Virginia
    - [47.001] State budget, amendments, 1989. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - [47.001] State budget, amendments, 1989. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - [47.001-A] Appropriations, 1992. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - [47.001-E] Opportunity Knocks, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - [47.001-E] Budget cuts, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - [47.001-E (1)] Law enforcement, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - [47.001-E (3)] General correspondence, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - [47.001-E (4)] Education, 1995. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - [47.002] Correspondence, General, 1989-1992. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - [47.003] Appointments by Governor, 1985-1992. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - [47.003-A] Term appointments, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - [47.003-C] Gubernatorial appointments, 1994. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - [47.005] Budget, 1989. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - [47.006] Budget requests, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - [47.007] Designated spokesmen, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - [47.008] Budget and requests, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - [47.008] Budget- House Appropriation Committee, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - [47.008] Budget- General, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - [47.008] Budget- Aid to localities, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - [47.008] Budget- Mental Health services, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - [47.008] Budget- Consolidation of Social Services Management, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - [47.008] Budget- Emergency services, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - [47.008] Budget- Dept. of Corrections, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - [47.008] Budget- Constitutional offices, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - [47.008] Budget- Education, 1990-1991. (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - [47.008] Budget- Private museums, 1990-1991. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - [47.008] Budget- Governors proposals, 1990-1991. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - [47.008-A] Revenue shortfall, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - [47.008-A] Revenue shortfall, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - [47.008-B] Budget correspondence, 1992. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - [47.008-D] Budget, 1994. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - [47.008-D] Budget, 1994. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - [47.009] Governor's Rural Development Conference, 1990-1991. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - [47.010] Correspondence concerning budget cuts and elimination of services- Medical records program, 1992. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - [47.010-A] Correspondence concerning budget cuts and elimination of services- Public tv, 1992. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - [47.010-C] Correspondence concerning budget cuts and elimination of services- Cooperative Extension Services, 1992. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - [47.010-C] Correspondence concerning budget cuts and elimination of services- Cooperative Extension Services, 1992. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - [47.010-E] Correspondence concerning budget cuts and elimination of services- Cooperative Extension Services, 1995. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission- Sentencing and Parole, 1994. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - [47.011] Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform Governor's Commission, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - [47.013] Blue Ribbon Strike Force Governor's Commission on Government Reform, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - [47.013] Blue Ribbon Strike Force Governor's Commission on Government Reform, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - [47.013] Blue Ribbon Strike Force Governor's Commission on Government Reform, 1994. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - [47.013] Blue Ribbon Strike Force Governor's Commission on Government Reform, 1994. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - [47.013] Blue Ribbon Strike Force Governor's Commission on Government Reform, 1994. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - [47.014] Election of Donald E. Beyer for Governor, 1997. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - [47.015] Governor's Legislative Proposal, 1999. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 48. Criminal Justice Service, Dept.
    - [48.001] Criminal Justice Service Department General Correspondence- Pre Trail Diversion Report, 1998. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - 49. Police and militia
    - [49.001] Virginia State Defense Force, 1987-1989. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - [49.002] Polygraphs, 1987-1988. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - 50. State songs
    - [50.001] Virginia State Song- Frank Riles, 1987. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - [50.003] Virginia State Song (includes record), 1988. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - 51. U.S. Constitution
    - [51.001] Constitutional Amendments- Equal Rights Amendment, 1981-1988. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - 52. Taxation, Dept.
    - [52.001-A] Evaluation of Sales Tax Exemption Requests Study 1993. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - [52.003] Food and Beverage Tax, 1986-1989. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - [52.003] Food and Beverage Tax, 1999. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - [52.004] Taxation on religious enterprises, 1987. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - [52.006] Sales tax and 1989 tax refund, 1988-1989. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - [52.007] IRA's counted as cash assets for real estate taxes, 1987-1989. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - [52.009] State recordation tax revenue, 1989. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - [52.009-A] H.B. 689 Exemptions from the recordation tax, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - [52.010] General correspondence, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - [52.011] CPA General, Wilder appearance, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - [52.012] Income tax age subtraction, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - [52.013] Tax exemption on real estate and vehicles for persons over 65 or handicapped, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - [52.014] Tax credits for the elderly, 1992. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - [52.015] Back taxes owed Commonwealth, 1992. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - [52.016] Literacy Volunteers of America- Sales and use tax exemption, 1993. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - [52.019] Tax Exemption- Young Live of Virginia, Inc., 1995. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - [52.020] H.B. 1499 Property tax exemption, 1995. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - [52.022] Tax Exemption- AMVETS, 1996-1997. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - [52.023] Tax exemption for Northwest Recreation Club, 1996. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - [52.024] Tax Exemption- Copies Furnished by Professionals Incident to Performing Professional Services, 1996-1997. (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - [52.025] Tax Exemption- Food Purchases for Nonprofit schools and colleges, 1996. (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - 53. Treasury, Dept.
    - [53.001] Unclaimed property within 16th district, 1985-1991. (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - [53.002] Governor's Tax Reform Act, 1987. (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - [53.003] Preliminary annual report of the State Treasurer, 1987. (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - [53.004] Bond issues, 1992. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - 55. Agriculture & Consumer Services, Dept.
    - [55.001] Coalition for Pets, 1986-1990. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - [55.002] Credit repair clinics, 1988. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - [55.003] S.B. 235 Petroleum Products Franchise Act, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - [55.003] S.B. 235 Petroleum Products Franchise Act, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - [55.003-A] General correspondence- Petroleum products, 1992. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - [55.004] Meat and Poultry meat inspection, 1990-1991. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - [55.005] CRESPA Violation, 1998. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 56. Secretary of Finance
    - [56.001] Virginia State Lottery, 1987-1993. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - [56.001] Virginia State Lottery, 1987-1993. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - [56.001] Virginia State Lottery, 1987-1993. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - [56.001] Virginia State Lottery, 1987-1993. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - [56.001] Virginia State Lottery, 1987-1993. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - [56.001-A] State Lottery Building, 1993-1994. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - [56.002] Virginia Racing Commission, 1989-1990. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - [56.003] Riverboat gambling, 1994-1995. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - [56.003] Riverboat gambling, 1994-1995. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - [56.003] Riverboat gambling, 1994-1995. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - [56.003] Riverboat gambling, 1994-1995. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - [56.004] Sub-Committee on Bingo and Raffle, 1993-1997. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - [56.004] Sub-Committee on Bingo and Raffle, 1993-1997. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - [56.004] Sub-Committee on Bingo and Raffle, 1993-1997. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 58. Corporation, Insurance & Banking General
    - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - [58.001-A] Legislation affecting banking, 1987-1990. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - [58.001-B] H.B. 141 Nonprofit debt counseling agencies, 1990. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - [58.001-C] H.B. 533 Insurable interest in life insurance policies, 1988. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - [58.002-A] H.B. 1238 Bank's limitations on obligations of borrowers, 1987. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - [58.002-B] H.B. 334 Voting entitlement of shares under the Stock Corporation Act, 1990. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, Correspondence, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, Against, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - [58.002-C] H.B. 335 Licensing of lending institutions to sell classes of insurance, 1991. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - [58.003-A] H.B. 1170 Bank mergers, 1987. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - [58.003-B] Public Service Corporations, 1988-1989. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - [58.003-C] General correspondence, Insurance, 1988-1989. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - [58.004-A] H.B. 1114 Bank branch and trust offices, 1987. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - [58.004-B] H.B. 137 Shareholders' derivative suits, 1992. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - [58.004-C] H.B. 1195 Reimbursement under accident and health insurance plans for services performed by certain persons, 1989. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - [58.005-A] H.B. 1111 Bank's acquisition of or loans on its own stock, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - [58.005-C] H.B. 178 Coverage of newly born children under health insurance policies, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - [58.006-A] H.B. 1110 Multiple party accounts, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - [58.006-C] Credit life insurance, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - [58.007-A] H.B. 1109 Deposits and collections in the separate office of a bank, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - [58.007-C] Insurance coverage for infertility treatment, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - [58.008-A] H.B. 1108 Bank loans to officers and directors, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - [58.009-A] H.B. 1027 Banking changes, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - [58.010-A] H.B. 1026 Money orders, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - [58.011-A] H.B. 1020 Fees for supervision and regulation of banks and savings institutions, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - [58.012-A] H.B. 1404 Bank's authority to pledge assets for the sale and repurchase of securities, 1989. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - [58.013-A] H.B. 1406 Bank's ownership and leasing of personal property, 1989. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - [58.014-A] H.B. 1407 Banks investments authority, 1989. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - [58.014-A] H.B. 1407 Banks investments authority, 1989. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - [58.016-A] H.B. 142 Special examinations of savings institutions, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - [58.017-A] H.B. 143 Consumer loans charges, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - [58.018-A] S.J.R. 39 Financial institution and real estate brokers and agents, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - [58.019-A] S.B. 602 Rules of 78's, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - [58.019-A] S.B. 602 Rules of 78's, 1990. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - [58.020-A] H.B. 1358 Limits on bank loans, 1992. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - [58.021] Credit Union common bond requirements, 1997. (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - 59. Courts of Justice
    - [59.001] House Committee for Courts of Justice, 1989-1990. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - [59.001] House Committee for Courts of Justice, 1989-1990. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - [59.001-A] Civil Court, H.B. 152 Rule 11 Frivolous claims on notions, 1990. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - [59.001-B] Criminal Court, Capital punishment for mentally retarded, 1989. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - [59.001-C] Domestic Relations, H.J.R. 301 Marital rape, 1985-1986. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - [59.001-D] Administration, H.B. 6 Computer crime bill, 1983-1987. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - [59.001-D] Administration, H.B. 6 Computer crime bill, 1983-1987. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - [59.002-A] H.B. 1319 Embezzlement of personal property, 1989. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - [59.002-B] H.B. 1324 Chemical tests to determine the alcohol or drug content of blood, 1989. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - [59.002-C] H.B. 508 Recording testimony, 1990. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - [59.002-D] General, 1990. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - [59.003-A] H.B. 1405 Copies of originals which may be used as evidence, 1989. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - [59.003-B] H.B. 278 Presumption of negligence, 1990. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - [59.003-C] S.B. 196 Spousal support, 1992. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - [59.003-D] Judicial Council Time Standards, 1991. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - [59.004-A] H.B. 1228 Deed cover sheet, 1989. (Box 69, Folder 8)